people throw what your channel is called
людей бросишь как ваш канал называется
blogger channel like which blog went by god
блогер как какой блоге прошла богом
immediately sat there in a clown costume
сразу садились там в костюм клоуна
discount specially the plot of the head of the
скидку специально сюжетом головы
audience
зрителей была у
you had a lot of such clones.  almost
вас много таких клонов . чуть не на
serious how it is here I have blogged
серьезную как она вот у меня я blogged
andrey folders my channel is
андрей папок у меня канал
understandable no one channel share
понятно никого канал делитесь
you ukrainians have specially chosen in
вы украины специально выбрали
common I have all the country I wanted to
общего у меня все страну стоят я хотел
talk about this issue with people from
поговорить о таком вопросе с людьми из
russia because everything on your
россии потому что у вас все на
constitutions is very good if  for example,
конституциях очень хорошо если например
Zelinsky will take it and
зелинский возьмет и и станкам
shoot parliament with machines, this will be
расстреляет парламент это будет
constitutionally a
конституционно
fish tank, but about shooting at orlando,
fish tank а про стреляет по орландо
look, I understood this, except for the simpsons
смотрите я понял это разве к симпсонам
on issues of
по вопросам
institutional cage, or rather, there was
клетка институционный вернее было
quality in the fourth year when you
качество на четвертом году когда у вас
don’t have a commandment and let’s not move out and the
не заповедь и давайте не съезжать и
walls, look, I understood this  so I’m
стены смотри я понял так вот я вас
just [ __ ] you a little and answering to
просто немножко долбать и ответить
shoot as many for one of them
расстреливать столько for one их
normally
нормально
answer the question we
ответь ответе на вопрос у нас
had it for the Joseon people died there
это было к чосона люди там погибли
agreed agreed that what kind of
договорили договорили что того какое
scoreboard we spoke we were completely savvy
табло говорили мы совсем подкованная
I’ll say agreed tell me the article of
скажу договорили назовите мне статью
your constitution agreed on which
вашей конститу договорились по которой
it was  the whole wheel is on the agreement, I am
она это было все колесо на договорили я
listening to the article, I am waiting, I say we have agreed on the
слушаю статью жду я говорю договорили
agreement  or
договорили
now you shut your mouth now I’m
теперь вы закрываете рот теперь я
telling you agreed ok yes, then
рассказываю договорились ok да значит
look in the fourteenth year, the elimination
смотрите в четырнадцатом году устранение
of Yanukovych was absolutely
к януковичу было абсолютно
constitutional because
конституционно потому что
we have the only body that
у нас есть единственный орган который
can determine the constitutionality or
может определять конституционность или
non-constitutionality of a military but
не конституционность воин но
normative legal act, and this is a
нормативно-правовой акт а это есть
constitutional court no appeals from
конституционный суд никаких обращений от
Yanukovych from a deputy from the Party of Regions, the
януковича от депутата от партии регионов
world did not have a sensational court on this
мир сенсационный суд не было по этому
issue, therefore, I don’t, you don’t determine
вопросу поэтому не я не вы не определяет
the constitutionality of unconstitutional,
и конституционность неконституционных а
but in the ninety-third year, when
вот в девяносто третьем году когда
Yeltsin your president shot
ельцин ваш президент расстреливал
parliament, you also had a
парламент вот у вас тоже был
constitutional crisis, that is, he
конституционный кризис то есть он
dissolved the parliament parliament said
распустил парламент парламент сказал что
that Yeltsin does not have the authority to dissolve
у ельцина нет полномочий распускать так
and so the constitutional court of the Russian Federation sued for
и подались конституционный суд
consideration and then the Germans drove the
рассмотрения и тогда немцы подогнал
tanks to the parliament shot by the
танки к парламенту расстреливал
parliament 157 people you killed were
парламентом 157 человек у вас убита была
troops to the parliament drove how do you feel
войска на парламент подогнал как вы
about where you can see
относитесь к где можно посмотреть
you answer no  you need to check, take,
вам отвечать не нужно проверить возьмите
take, google this Yasinsky
возьмите загуглить этом ясинский
coup of 93, here is a riot of silver
переворотом 93 год вот буйством серебро
93 awards and documents what exactly is
93 наград и документов что именно е
each note,
каждая нота а
but look,
вот смотрите
google it, yes, right now, let
загуглите да вот прям сейчас давайте
's
разберемся как
see how you can take the Yeltsin coup of
там можете возьмите ельцинский переворот
93, it will give you a bunch of material,
93 года она вам выдаст кучу материала
maybe even us now you  you can
может даже нами теперь вы можете
see if you trust her don’t
посмотреть если ей доверяетесь не
trust other materials,
доверяйте другие материалы
but I don’t see anything like that where
но я ничего подобного не вижу где
it says the projection on what he drove the
написано проекцию на что он подгонял
tanks and who drove them,
танки а кто подогнал
but where do you show me the documents what do you
но где вот мне покажи документы что вы
call it in this and so the tool is
что в этой назвать и так что инструмент
not for some articles here  very
не на какие-то статьи тут их очень
much that you discovered
многого что вы открыли
that that you discovered that I was supposed to be
что что вы открыли что я крылся быть
wikipedia wikipedia of the year before wikipedia
википедию википедией года до википедия
how do you do tatyana set
как у вас татьяна задавать
events september october 93 at 3 4 to
события сентябрь октябрь 93 в 3 4 до
moscow yes super yes
москве да супер да
well you won’t drive in I don’t see that there
ну не въедешь я не вижу чтоб есть
drove away but so let’s read between
отогнал но так давайте читать между
between  those who were the conflict
между теми кем были был конфликт
no you tell me where else what were
нет вы мне скажите где еще какие были
what were the supporters you let's you
какие были сторонники вы давайте вот вы
read what  you had parties to the conflict in
прочитали какие стороны конфликта были у
the ninety-third year, look, I
вас девяносто третьем году смотрите я
’m going to lose a lot of creation now,
сейчас сотворение буду очень много
so let’s let me wait
терять что вот давайте давайте я подожду
answered
ответили
now we’ll figure out that you didn’t cope
сейчас разберемся что вы не справились
with that and our roots are our sputum, let’s
с тем и коренья мокроте наш давайте
someone don’t interrupt the elder, I’m older than you,
кто не перебивайте старшего я старше вас
don’t interrupt
не перебивайте
turn on the sound,
включу звук
let’s
давайте
Yeltsin  yeltsin illegally
ельцин ельцин незаконно в девяносто
shot your parliament in 1993 and
третьем году расстрелял ваш парламент и
killed 157 civilians what do you say
убили 157 мирных человек что скажете
screen it was mowed down in the zone let's
screen это был косит зоне давайте
ninety-three year
девяносто третий год
ninety-three it was hanging out
девяносто третий год это было тусуется
for murder,
на убийство
that is, you got burnt see how
то есть вы вас подгорел видите как
burnt why because since 93
подгорело почему потому что с 93 года у
you don't have  of the constitution you are an illegal
вас нету конституции вас незаконная
kurta in power where since 93 let
курта при власти где с 93 года давайте
subscribers watch the show in the wrong place I’ve been writing since
подписчикам смотрите шоу не там пишу с
93 since 93 you have a dick then in
93 года с 93 года у вас хуем то при
power that is, let me think yes
власти то есть давайте я вам кажется да
turn them off wave the handle
выключаем их махнете ручкой
since 93 yes I
с 93 года да я сейчас для подписчиков
’ll tell subscribers now how  since you turned off the sound, I’m
расскажу как раз вы отключили звук я вам
bored to you too in the ninety-third year in
тоже скуки девяносто третьем году в
Russia,
россии так
a military coup happened and ate  tsin
случился военный переворот а ельцин
illegally dissolved the parliament when it was
незаконно распустил парламент когда это
impossible to do so according to the constitution so
нельзя было делать по конституции так
let him violate the constitution the parliament
пусть он нарушил конституцию парламент
said that the constitution was
обратился что конституция
violated and appealed to the constitutional
нарушена и обратился в конституционный
court yeltsin so drove the troops the president
суд ельцин так подогнал войска президент
drove the troops to the parliament
погнал войска в на парламент
shot parliaments from tanks I was
расстреливал из танков парламентах я был
small and I remember it from the video so for
маленький и помню это по видео так для
I was in shock, I lived in Ukraine already
меня это была в шоке я жил в украине уже
independent, so we saw that he was there,
независимый так и мы видели что он там
that Rick was interesting, but
что рик интересно а вот
Russian, study your history since 93
русский изучайте свою историю с 93 года
, you had an illegal seizure of power,
у вас произошел незаконный захват власти
so your country has been under the
так ваша страна находится с 93 года под
rule of the junta since 93, so the junta that
властью хунты так хунта которая
shot  parliament, the laws of the legally
расстреляла парламент законы законно
elected and
избранного так и
sorted it out,
разобрала
I don’t hear something for the car, so
я вас не слышу что-то машине так вот
study Russian, google the events of this
изучать вот загуглите события этом 3 4
October 3, 1993 in Moscow you will see how the
октября 93 года в москве вы увидите как
cruel fascist regime killed its
жестокий фашистский режим убивал своих
own people
же людей
killed its own people so the
убивал своих людей так
peasant dances
мужик танцует
andstaged
и поставлены
[music  ]
[музыка]
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
dude something staggers sit
чувак что-то шатается сидеть
rickets
рахит
in  go to this blog blogger for a second, he’s
ведь и это блоге блогер секунда он
even afraid to tell us there that there
боится даже сказать к нам там что там
’s something to talk with his distant
что то разговаривать со своими дальними
dude won’t turn off
чувак не отключит
heard
услышала
write
пишите
Russians you have been living since
россияне вы живете с
93 state
93 года государственном
yes
да
plush these glasses of mine I’ll turn off the
вот эти стекло свой я сейчас отключу
sound now but then they’ll sit you then with
звук но так посидят вам тогда с
with a muted sound, they are all here
отключенным звуком они все те тут
talking about the facts, how it comes to the fact
говорить по фактам как доходит до факт
they explode farts and compare, I
они взрываются пердаки и сравни я тебе
’ll turn off the sound for you now, yes, because so that
сейчас отключу звук да потому что чтобы
these viewers don’t hear the facts, they don’t
их не эти зрители не слышали фактов не
really hear what
слышали действительно того что
happened, look how interesting,
происходило вот смотрите как интересно
yes, they all come in for that  so that
да они все заходят для того чтобы что-то
there is something about 2014 in this, we had absolutely
там про 2014 год в этом у нас абсолютно
everything mines, we had the
все было мин у нас
Verkhovna Rada did not shoot the
верховная рада не расстреливал этом
President of the President did not shoot the
президента президента не расстрелял
Verkhovna Rada before they shot him
верховную раду до отстрелили его
due to the fact that he himself was eliminated if
связи с тем что он сам устранился если
this is a man I think that yes,
это мужик считаю что да
unconstitutional where is the decision of the
неконституционным где решение
constitutional court  where to this is the filing
конституционного суда где к это подача
before the constitutional court of this issue
до в конституционный суд этого вопроса
was not, and that is, the body is prescribed in the constitution
не было а то есть есть в конституции
the order by which
прописано органа порядок которым
legal acts, including the
нормативно-правовые акты в том числе
resolution of the Verkhovna Rada, are
постановление верховной рады
determined constitutional or
определяются конституционным или
unconstitutional if there is some
неконституционным если есть кое-то
doubt about the league of constitutionality, so the
сомнение лиги конституционности так у
dude just picks up at 93 points of
чувака вот просто подбирает при 93 балла
labor, then I understand he wants to cut off
труда то-то я понимаю он хочет срезать
cursing him answered come back to 93 and
проклиная ему ответил возвращайся в 93 и
he  to give you 2, then no, he doesn’t have the
он вам передать по 2 то нету нету у него
courage to even admit that since 93,
смелости даже признать что с 93 года
when Yeltsin seized
когда ельцин захватил
power in the country, in fact, by a military
власть в стране фактически военным
coup, so after that, back there
переворотом так после этого еще там туда
in the ninety-ninth year, the FSB tires
в девяносто девятом году фсб шинах унтас
untas still displaced Yeltsin, renounced on
еще сместила ельцина отрекся в
New Year’s Eve, in my opinion, there is a night from  of its throne,
новогоднем по-моему там ночь от престола
russia is a country a coup in a
своего россия это страна переворот в
country in which there is no democracy in
страна в которой нету демократии в
which the military junta has been in power for many years
которой военная хунта уже сколько лет
and has been killing civilians
держит власть и убивает мирных граждан
so in the ninety-third year 157 people were killed
так девяносто третьем году убили 157
with a tank they were shot
человек с танком расстреливали так
because russia wants to
потому что россия хочет
destabilize everything around it
дестабилизировать все вокруг себя для
so that the inhabitants would not see  what kind of
того чтобы не видели жители россии какое
[ __ ] is done in russia
[__] делается в россии русские
russians wake up open  open your eyes because
просыпайтесь открывайте глаза потому что
you need to get rid of this
вам надо освобождаться от этой пункты
item in ukraine
по украине